dkny.com 2014-02-09

# DKNY Legal - DKNY

This website, which is located at [www.dkny.com](http://www.dkny.com/) (the “Site”), is published and maintained by The Donna Karan Company LLC and The Donna Karan Company Store LLC, 550 Seventh Avenue, New York, New York 10018, +1-877-316-0975 (collectively, "DKC" or “we” or “us”). This Privacy Policy applies to your access to and use of the Site and any other website, microsite, mobile device application, Internet property or related service owned or operated by us. We refer to the Site and these other properties collectively as the "Properties.” Please read through carefully to understand our practices regarding personal information and how we use and treat it. By visiting the Properties, and/or using the related services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our services, this Privacy Policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time. In certain circumstances, you may be notified of such changes by email, text, SMS or other means. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the DKNY Terms of Use, which governs your use of the Properties.   

NOTE FOR INTERNATIONAL USERS: If you are accessing the Site from outside of the United States of America and place an order, you agree to and will be subject to the [Terms & Conditions](http://www.borderfree.com/terms) and [Privacy Policy](http://www.borderfree.com/privacy) of DKC’s international fulfillment partner, Borderfree, Inc., 292 Madison Avenue, Fifth Floor, New York, New York 10017, +1-212-299-3500 (“Borderfree”). Please review Borderfree’s terms and policies before placing an order with Borderfree. Borderfree may share information with us and, in that event, we will treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.   

**PURPOSE**   

Your privacy is a serious matter to us. In order to make your visits to the Properties and use of the related services as worthwhile as possible, we may ask you for Personal Information and we may collect certain information from your computer each time you visit us. "Personal Information" includes, for example, your name; your username on third-party social media sites; home and/or business address; e-mail address; telephone, mobile, wireless and/or fax number; short message service or text message address or other wireless device address; instant messaging address; credit/debit card and other payment information; location information; language preferences; demographic information and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual. This Privacy Policy explains, in general, what Personal Information and other information is collected via the Properties, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information. Please take a few minutes to read our Privacy Policy so that you understand how DKC treats your information.   

**RIGHT TO OPT OUT**   

You have the right to "opt-out" of certain of our uses of your Personal Information at any time. For example, at the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on the Properties, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to: (1) receive correspondence from us, or (2) have your Personal Information shared with other entities for their marketing purposes. (We will not share, sell or trade your Personal Information with other entities outside of the LVMH Family for their marketing purposes without your permission. See the "Do we share Personal Information and Usage Information with others?" section below for more information about our data sharing practices.) You may also make this request by visiting our [unsubscribe page](http://www.dkny.com/pages/help#unsubscribe). You may also opt-out of DKC's promotional e-mails at any time by clicking on an opt-out link within the e-mail you receive.   
Please understand that if you opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions, and communications with us. Also, a request to have us stop sharing your Personal Information with other entities for marketing purposes will only apply as of the date of your request, and we will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from entities that received your Personal Information prior to such request. In these cases, please contact that entity directly.   
You can also control certain cookies and tracking tools. To learn more about our tracking and how to manage how we – and our vendors – use cookies and other tracking tools, please [click here](http://www.dkny.com/pages/legal/#about-ads)   

**What Information is Collected?**   

**USER-PROVIDED INFORMATION**   

We may collect Personal Information from users of our Properties, for example, through such users' activities, transactions and completion of online forms on the Properties. Such information is collected, for example, when users register or subscribe for accounts, electronic newsletters, or features on our Properties, make online purchases, enter sweepstakes and contests, complete surveys, post materials, contribute to a chat room, bulletin board, list serve, blog, wiki or other open forum that we may make available on or through our Properties, submit a comment or question to us using a "Contact Us" or similar feature on our Properties, send us an e-mail, or in any other way submit Personal Information to us via our Properties.   
You may be able to send information about our products and services to your friends and family members through the Properties by clicking on an "E-mail to Friend" or similar button on the Properties or in an e-mail that we have sent you. In some of these cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may provide the name and e-mail address of your friend or family member to us. You should only do this if you know your friend or family member would consent to such sharing. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.   
You may also be able to send an online card or message to a friend or family member, or send them a gift or gift certificate. If so, you may be required to provide us with your friend's or family member's Personal Information. You should only do this if you know your friend or family member would consent to such sharing. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.   
NOTE FOR INTERNATIONAL USERS: The Personal Information that we collect from you or that we may receive from our third-party vendors, including Borderfree, may be transferred to, and stored at, locations in the United States of America, outside of the country or other economic area in which you reside (including the European Economic Area (“EEA”)). The information may also be processed by staff who work for DKC, its affiliates, or its service providers, and who are located outside of the country or economic area (including the EEA) in which you reside. Such staff may engage in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your Personal Information and engaging with the Properties, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. DKC will take reasonable steps to ensure that your Personal Information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.   

**USAGE INFORMATION**   

We may automatically collect anonymous Usage Information that does not identify an individual user ("Usage Information"). For example, each time you use the Properties we may automatically collect the type of web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to such Properties. We use this information to help us understand how people use Properties, and to enhance the products and services we offer.   

**COOKIES**   

We may use "cookies" to keep, and sometimes track, analytics and information about you. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a web server and stored on your computer's or mobile device’s hard drive. Cookies track where you travel on the Properties and what you look at and purchase. They may store the information in your shopping cart, wish list and/or your username and/or password. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of the Properties to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on the Properties, to determine which areas and features of the Properties are most popular, and to make improvements and updates to enhance the Properties experience.   
If you do not wish to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser preferences to refuse them or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To disable cookies, please consult your browser’s “help” section for instructions. Additionally, if you have a Flash player installed on our computer, your Flash player can be set to reject or delete Flash cookies. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Properties or certain areas or features of the Properties including preventing you from purchasing products from the Properties.   

**CLEAR GIFS**   

We may use "clear GIFs" (aka "web beacons" or "pixel tags") or similar technologies, in the Properties and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual's viewing or receipt of a web page or message. A clear gif may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information.   

**IP ADDRESS AND CLICKSTREAM DATA**   

Our server automatically collects data about your server's Internet address when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you are on the Internet. When you request pages from the Properties, our servers may log your IP Address, domain name, location, language preferences and other aggregate information. Our servers may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another website or a search engine); the pages you visit on the Properties; the website you visit after the Properties; the ads you see and/or click on; your product interests and purchases; other information about the type of web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on the Properties or a referral site; and other web usage activity and data logged by our web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Properties. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with your Personal Information. Any or all of these activities with regard to website Usage Information may be performed on our behalf by our services providers including, for example, Borderfree and Linkshare.   

**HOW IS THE PERSONAL INFORMATION USED?**   

We will use the Personal Information you provide to the Properties, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings. For example, we will process your orders, respond to your requests and inquiries and provide you with the products, services and features offered on or through the Properties. We may also use your Personal Information to help us develop and improve the Properties, tailor the Properties to your interests, and maintain our internal record keeping. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both Personal Information and Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies, promotions, contests and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. DKC may offer electronic newsletters and e-mails as a service to our users. You will only receive a newsletter or promotional e-mail from DKC if you agree during your activities on or through the Properties, or using our newsletter sign up form, to receive these items. Unsubscribe instructions are included in each electronic newsletter and e-mail. You may opt-out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above, or by submitting a request through the “Contact Us” feature on our website or Properties. We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, the Properties and e-mails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate. We may also use the Personal Information for fraud protection or credit risk reduction.   

**Do we share Personal Information and Usage Information with others?**   

**THE LVMH FAMILY**   

DKC is part of the LVMH Moët Hennessy Louis Vuitton (“LVMH”) corporate family. DKC, together with LVMH and LVMH's other affiliates, are collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as the “LVMH Family." Unless you instruct us otherwise as described in the Right to Opt Out section above, we will share your Personal Information and Usage Information among the LVMH Family, both for business purposes and for advertising and promotional purposes. A list of the current members of the LVMH Family may be found at [www.lvmh.com](http://www.lvmh.com/).   

**CO-SPONSORED CONTESTS, SWEEPSTAKES AND OFFERINGS**   

Some of our contests, sweepstakes and other offerings that we may make available on or through the Properties from time to time may be co-sponsored by another company. In those situations, unless you instruct us otherwise, the information we obtain from you in connection with such contest, sweepstake or offering may be shared with our co-sponsor and in accordance with any specific terms disclosed in such contest or sweepstakes. In those situations, our co-sponsors will have the right to use your information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies and in particular in accordance with any specific disclosures made to you at the time you participate in such contest or sweepstakes. We are not responsible for how our co-sponsors may use your information.   

**SERVICE PROVIDERS**   

Currently, we use third party partners to provide our e-commerce solution, and we may use other third party partners to help operate the Properties and deliver our products and services. We may share your information with third party e-commerce solution partners, third-party payment providers (e.g., Visa, Mastercard and American Express), our affiliates, service providers, and other third parties that provide products or services for or through the Properties or for our business (such as Properties hosting or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, wireless device applications, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). We require our service providers to maintain the confidentiality of your Personal Information.

**AGGREGATE STATISTICS**   

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, the Properties and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user. Aggregate information is non-personally identifiable/anonymous information about you, such as age, gender, types of products purchased, pages you access most frequently or search terms you enter. Aggregate information is used in a collective manner, and no single person can be identified by that compiled information. For example, the number of people who visit www.dkny.com who are 25 years of age is aggregate information that does not personally identify a specific user.   

**LEGALLY COMPELLED DISCLOSURES**   

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required by law in our good faith belief, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas and as otherwise required in connection with a judicial or government proceeding or legal process, including in relation to the enforcement of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Properties, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. DKC cooperates with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property rights and other rights.   

**BUSINESS TRANSFER**   

In the event that DKC, any entity of the LVMH Family, or substantially all of its assets, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.   

**THIRD PARTY AD SERVERS**   

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Properties. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to the Properties and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear gifs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear gifs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your Personal Information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies and to opt out, see the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer website at [www.networkadvertising.org/consumer-education](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer-education).   

**WIRELESS ADDRESSES**   

If the email address you provide to us is a wireless email address, you agree to receive messages at such address from DKC and the rest of the LVMH Family (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above). You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates apply to these messages, and that you may change your mind at any time by following the instructions in the Right to Opt Out section above. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.   

**YOUR ACCESS RIGHTS**   

You may review the Personal Information that is stored in your user account on www.dkny.com by logging in at "My Account", or by calling our customer service department at +1-877-316-0975. We will send you a copy of the Personal Information we have on file in your user account (if any). You may provide us new or updated information at any time. We will endeavor to respond to your request to access, update or delete your information as soon as practicable. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details to help us to respond to your request.   

**SECURITY**   

Protecting your information is a priority for DKC. DKC will take reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all Personal Information provided to the Properties. For example, we use industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your sensitive online transactions and we store and process your Personal Information on secured servers. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of DKC to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, DKC cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.   
If you contact us by e-mail, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit.   
You may be able to create an account on the Properties with a username and password. If so, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the Properties by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you, and whether or not such person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to (a) immediately notify DKC of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. It is your sole responsibility to control the dissemination and use of your password, control access to and use of your account, and notify DKC when you desire to cancel your account on the Properties. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, (x) we will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision and (y) you agree to indemnify and hold harmless DKC and other members of the LVMH Family for any improper, unauthorized or illegal use of your account.   
We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission.   
In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.   

**PHISHING**   

With identity theft a continuing problem, it has become increasingly common for unauthorized individuals purporting to represent a legitimate company such as a bank or on-line merchant, to send e-mail messages to consumers requesting that the consumer provide personal, often sensitive information. Sometimes, the domain name of the e-mail address from which the e-mail appears to have been sent, and the domain name of the website requesting such information, appears to be the domain name of a legitimate, trusted company. In reality, such sensitive information is received by an unauthorized individual to be used for purposes of identity theft. This illegal activity is known as "phishing."   
If you receive an e-mail or other correspondence requesting that you provide any sensitive information (including your Properties password or credit/debit card information) via e-mail or to a website that does not seem to be affiliated with the Properties, or that otherwise seems suspicious to you, please do not provide such information, and report such request to us by calling 1-877-316-0975 or by submitting a report through the “Contact Us” feature on our website or Properties.   

**CHILDREN AND PRIVACY**   

DKC is concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the sites their children visit. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 (or other age where parental consent may be required) without prior verifiable parental consent when legally required. If we become aware that a customer has registered without the legally required prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information from our files.   
Information posted to message boards, chat areas, club and home pages are available to the general public. Please use caution when posting any such information. Users under the age of 18 should be particularly careful not to provide any personally identifying information while using chat rooms, message boards, or any other public forums. Users of chat areas, message boards, or any other public forums must follow acceptable standards of behavior when posting messages online. DKC reserves the right to, but is not obligated to, refuse or delete any content that in our sole discretion is considered inappropriate.   

**CONSENT TO PROCESSING**   

This website is hosted and operated in the United States of America, pursuant to United States law and this Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States of America. By providing Personal Information to this website, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States of America and other countries and territories.   
NOTE FOR INTERNATIONAL USERS: If you are a user located in a member state of the EEA, please be aware that the laws of the United States of America and other countries and territories may not provide legal protection of your Personal Information that is of the same level as that applicable under the laws of the EEA member state in which you are located.   

**THIRD PARTY "LINKED-TO" WEBSITES**   

When you are on the Properties you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other sites not operated by DKC, including other websites operated by other members of the LVMH Family or by unaffiliated third parties. These sites may collect Personal Information about you. DKC does not control sites that are operated by these entities and is not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other websites. The Privacy Policies of websites operated by other members of the LVMH Family are located on those sites.   

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**   

DKC reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of the Properties by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to www.dkny.com. Your continued use of the Properties constitutes your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy as changed. Under certain circumstances (for example, if we would like to use your Personal Information in a manner different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time of collection), we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as by sending you an e-mail.   

**CONTACT US**   

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may contact us by calling +1-877-316-0975, sending an email to privacy@dkintl.com, or by submitting a request through the “Contact Us” feature on our website or Properties. This website is sponsored by The Donna Karan Company LLC, 550 Seventh Avenue, New York, New York 10018.   

Effective Date: December 19, 2013
